PERSONAL DATA

OBJECTIVE: Pursuing a challenging job in a competitive field and delivering a higher standard of services.

Utilizing my abilities through education and experiences for the opportunity for professional growth

based on my performance.

DATE OF BIRTH: 7th April 1981

INTERESTS: Interacting with/and meeting people, helping others, reading

CAREER GOALS

Ensuring goals and objectives are accomplished in accordance with outlined priorities and requirements. My experience with various companies has allowed me to possess the skills in developing a good relationship with fellow workers and supervisory staff, in getting the job done as quickly, efficiently and with professionalism in mind.

WORK EXPERIENCES

- 1. FIRST CITIZENS BANK, CHAGUANAS On The Job Training
- 2. GENERAL HOSPITAL, SAN FERNANDO

1999 -2001

Medical Clerk

Computer Training – RHA IS/IT Department

3. DIAMOND SYSTEMS LIMITED

Data Entry Clerk/ Secretary for Managing Directors

4. TUCKER ENERGY SERVICES LIMITED – DRILLING DIVISION, LA

ROMAIN *March – June* 2008

Divisional Administrative Assistant (for Drilling)

5. ESCADA IMPORTS LIMITED - Hobson Street, San Fernando

2008-2010

Administrative Officer

Product Supervisor (chic ladies stockings)

6. ADAMS PROJECT MANAGEMENT AND CONSTRUCTION LTD,

COCORITE 2011 – 2012

Checker/ Stores Clerk/ Office Admin

7. PREM PERSAD MAHARAJ & COMPANY – ATTORNEYS AT LAW

2013 - 2014

Law Clerk/Office Mgr/Typist/Receptionist

- 8. PENAL MEDICAL ASSOCIATES
 - 3 months in 2016
 - 1. Assistant nurse checking temperatures, blood pressure, doing ECG, heart rate, weight/height
 - 2. And front desk clerk filling out patient information, learning medicines.

EDUCATION: COMPUTER EXPERIENCE

Also entails working in a computerized environment.

1. CHARLIES PREMIUM COMUTER CENTRE, SAN FERNANDO

Computer Technician Course GRADE A

2. MIS TRAINING ROOM

SOUTH WEST REGIONAL HEALTH AUTHORITY COMPUTER LITERACY

Microsoft Word Corel Print Word Microsoft Power Point Microsoft Excel Microsoft Publisher Internet Access Typing 50 w.p.m

CERTIFICATE OF ACHIEVEMENT

3. SERVOL HI-TECH, LA ROMAIN

COMPUTER LITERACY

Introduction to Computers

Dos and Windows

Word Processing – MS Word

Database – MS Access Spreadsheet – MS Excel

Bookkeeping and Accounting

GRADE A

4. ACHIEVED:

3_{RD} Place Certificate in Letter Writing Cambridge Information Technology Certificate – Microsoft Word

5. NATIONAL ENERGY SKILLS CENTRE (NESC)

August 2000 Computer Literacy Certificate of Completion

6. **OSHA ACT:** 30hrs Certified

7. MODERN BUSINESS SCHOOL LIMITED/ST. KEVINS COLLEGE

Principles of Business 1
English 2
Integrated Science 2
Social Studies 2
Math 3

Typing 55 - 60 wpm

CO CURRICULAR ACITIVITIES:

SELF ENHANCEMENT COURSES

Self Awareness

Punctuality and Attendance

Public Speaking

Communication Skills

Spirituality

Parenting

Group Counseling

Drama

Survival Cookery

Art Analysis

Effective Communication

Motivation

Personal Enhancement

Goal Setting And Accomplishment

Public Speaking and Presentations

Time Management

The Interview

Strategic Marketing

Business Etiquette

1. YOUTH TRAINING AND EMPLOYMENT PARTNERSHIP PROGRAM (YTEPP)

Six (6) Months Training For Each

2003

Career Enhancement Classes

2005

Micro Entrepreneurship

2. SINGER, CARLTON CENTRE, SAN FERNANDO

Three (3) Month Training Course

Dressmaking and Design

3. OPEN BIBLE CHURCH, PENAL

Former Head of Usher

Department

Prem Persad Maharaj

Prem Persad Maharaj & Co

Attoreny at Law

REFERENCES:

Shazahra Leia Khan-Camacho Sales Representative Guardian Life of the Caribbean 763-5886

763-5886 San Fernando
Pastor Tex Jones
Assistant Pastor

OTHERS AVAILABLE UPON YOUR REQUEST

CONTACT INFORMATION:

Open Bible Church

Penal 647-6772

• Contact #: 1-868-687-7450

• **Cell** #: 1-868-709-4501

☐ **Email:** <u>lisaramnarine@hotmail.com</u> OR <u>lisa.ramnarine@hotmail.com</u>

• Address: 11B Second Avenue, Vista Park, Freeport.